I think that
I
the shareholder
think
that
the
shareholder
base holding the
base
holding
the
MAG 6 they
MAG
have gotten so
they
have
gotten
so
used to
used
a hordes
to
a
hordes
and massive free
and
massive
free
cash flow
cash
generation that
flow
generation
that
this is a
this
big shock to
is
a
big
shock
to
them seeing these
them
hyperscalers take
seeing
these
hyperscalers
take
their capital
their
spending budgets
capital
spending
budgets
up 100 in
up
in
one year I
one
think Amazon announced
year
I
think
Amazon
announced
it would go
it
from roughly 90
would
go
from
roughly
billion to 180
billion
to
billion this
billion
year in
this
year
in
2026 That's
shocking to people
That's
shocking
to
people
And we're seeing
And
some of the
we're
seeing
some
of
the
MAG 6 raising
MAG
debt even
raising
debt
even
That has been
That
anathema to this
has
been
anathema
to
this
group So we
group
do think we're
So
we
do
think
we're
seeing a
seeing
shareholder turnover
a
shareholder
turnover
not massive because
not
of what I
massive
because
of
what
I
just described
just
about benchmarks
described
about
benchmarks
But we
But
don't think
we
don't
think
necessarily that they
necessarily
are doing the
that
they
are
doing
the
wrong things meaning
wrong
the hyperscalers We
things
meaning
the
hyperscalers
We
think Google is
think
doing the right
Google
is
doing
the
right
thing And all
thing
of the Amazon
And
all
of
the
Amazon
all of the
all
spending we think
of
the
spending
we
think
is the right
is
the
right